{
  "flashcards" : {
    "deck1" : {
      "cards" : [ {
        "back" : "Hamburger",
        "front" : "La hamburguesa"
      }, {
        "back" : "French fries",
        "front" : "Las papas fritas"
      }, {
        "back" : "Lettuce",
        "front" : "La lechuga"
      }, {
        "back" : "Chicken and rice",
        "front" : "El arroz con pollo"
      }, {
        "back" : "Bread",
        "front" : "El pan"
      } ],
      "name" : "Food"
    },
    "deck2" : {
      "cards" : [ {
        "back" : "Shirt",
        "front" : "La camisa"
      }, {
        "back" : "Pants",
        "front" : "Los pantalones"
      }, {
        "back" : "Shoes",
        "front" : "Los zapatos"
      }, {
        "back" : "Glasses",
        "front" : "Las gafas"
      }, {
        "back" : "Watch",
        "front" : "El reloj"
      } ],
      "name" : "Clothing and Accessories"
    }
  }
}
